<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on howinator howinatin</title>
    <link>https://howinator.io/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on howinator howinatin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:54:20 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://howinator.io/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 16 - Making Sense</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:54:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Something else I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about this quarantine is how little sense I&amp;rsquo;d be able to make of it all. On a daily basis, I oscillate between feeling like it&amp;rsquo;s the end of the world and everything is normal.
Like, within a one hour span, I&amp;rsquo;m refinancing my mortgage and reading an article about the coast guard telling cruise ships to turn away from American ports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 - USNS Comfort</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 21:46:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-14/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not a particularly patriotic person, but seeing the USNS Comfort sail into New York Harbor and dock at Pier 90 swelled with me nationalistic pride. Seeing the military arrive to assist the nation&amp;rsquo;s largest city isn&amp;rsquo;t something you witness many times in your lifetime.
In particular this video is just an awe-inspiring site. Just look at that shit. Every other time I&amp;rsquo;ve seen one of the Navy&amp;rsquo;s hospital shipts deployed, it&amp;rsquo;s been to a third-world country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 - Optimized Oven</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 21:35:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re an oven manufacturer facing shareholder pressure. Your goal is to make an oven that works for most customers as cheaply as possible. You realize most of your American customers live in houses that are temperature-controlled to 75 degrees Fahrenheit.
So, you start optimizing your oven to work in a 75 degree Fahrenheit environment. You rip out insulation. You install a temperature control system which works in a narrow range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intro</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 19:20:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>I finally got around to making my blog and hosting it on my infra woooo.
What you can expect from this blarg:
 Technology Personal Projects Politics Climate Change  If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to here about any of these topics, feel free to stick to the category or categories which interest you most.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>