<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>covid-19 on howinator howinatin</title>
    <link>https://howinator.io/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in covid-19 on howinator howinatin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 21:41:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://howinator.io/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Boredom</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 21:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-12/</guid>
      <description>The thing they don&amp;rsquo;t tell you about quarantine is how freaking grating th boredom is. Or, I don&amp;rsquo;t even know if it&amp;rsquo;s boredom, it&amp;rsquo;s just the absence of anything to be excited about.
Anyway, why aren&amp;rsquo;t auto-scaling groups controlled with a PID?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 - Optimized Oven</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 21:35:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re an oven manufacturer facing shareholder pressure. Your goal is to make an oven that works for most customers as cheaply as possible. You realize most of your American customers live in houses that are temperature-controlled to 75 degrees Fahrenheit.
So, you start optimizing your oven to work in a 75 degree Fahrenheit environment. You rip out insulation. You install a temperature control system which works in a narrow range.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 - Tech Therapeutics</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 21:55:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-day-10/</guid>
      <description>According to wiktionary, the word &amp;lsquo;therapeutic&amp;rsquo; comes from the greek word therapeutḗs, which is someone who &amp;ldquo;waits on another, an attendant&amp;rdquo;. As a software engineer, there&amp;rsquo;s not a whole lot I can do to affect the treatment of disease, a later meaning of the greek word. However, I can help help people wait on and attend to one another.
I started a project with a friend yesterday to connect people that need help and people that can provide help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7 - Shared Experience</title>
      <link>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-19-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 13:43:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://howinator.io/blog/covid-19-day-7/</guid>
      <description>The Covid-19 pandemic has to be the largest shared experience among humanity that we&amp;rsquo;re all experiencing separately. I can&amp;rsquo;t think of another episode in modern history where nearly every human experienced in their own way. And there really can&amp;rsquo;t be another event where we experienced completely separate from one another.
Think about something like 9/11. Only a few of us truly had to take some sort of action during 9/11. Some of us had to run away.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>